myxango.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy | XANGO

XANGO, LLC (“XANGO” or “we”) respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy documents our adherence to the highest industry standards for the protection of your personal information. By visiting XANGO web sites (“Site”) or using any of the services offered on the XANGO web sites, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 7, 2013 applies to information collected through the Site and covers the following areas: 

  * What personal information is collected by XANGO through the Site;
  * How XANGO uses this information;
  * With whom XANGO may share this information;
  * What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

XANGO has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  The TRUSTe program covers the websites in English [www.xango.com](http://www.xango.com/), Dutch [www.xango.nl](http://www.xango.nl/), French [www.xango.fr](http://www.xango.fr/), Italian [www.xango.it](http://www.xango.it/) and SPANISH [www.xango.com.es](http://www.xango.com.es/). The TRUSTe program does not cover mobile versions or applications of XANGO.  TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us [service@xango.com](mailto:service@xango.com).  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). 

XANGO complies with the U.S.–E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. XANGO has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view XANGO’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

**1\. Information Collection and Use**

XANGO collects information on the Site at two different stages. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information (such as domain name or IP address) from all visitors to the Site. This type of information is never linked to any personal information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical reports about the use of the Site. 

Second, we require the submission of certain personal information when you use the services available on the Site. For example, your use of your username and password allows us to identify you as a distributor of XANGO® products. We also collect billing and payment information such as your name, postal and email address. 

**2\. Personal Information of Children Under 13**

XANGO complies with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) and the FTC’s rule interpreting COPPA (16 CFR § 512). This Site is not directed to children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13 years of age through this Site. 

**3\. Use of Your Personal Information**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, XANGO does not sell, rent, or share user information to or with any third party not affiliated with or owned by XANGO, except service providers who may assist XANGO in areas such as data storage. XANGO will never give or sell your personal information to be used for the purposes of sending you unsolicited commercial offers (such as spam) from any third party. We will not ourselves use your personal information to send you unsolicited commercial offers. However, we may need to contact you for purposes other than marketing, as for example regarding the status of the Site, your account or other matters related to your role as a distributor of XANGO® products. You may not opt-out of these kinds of communications. If you wish to unsubscribe from our marketing emails, please follow the directions in the emails or go to the e-mail maintenance option in the account settings page. 

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering live chat customer support. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

**4\. Use of Aggregate Information**

We store information that we collect through log files to create a profile of our users. Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personal information. A profile is stored information detailing how individual users use the Site. It is used solely for internal purposes, to help us improve the experience of our users. We do not share your profile with any third parties. 

**5\. Tracking Technologies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.  

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. 

We set a persistent cookie to store your valid login, so you don’t have to login more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.” 

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.  Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. 

We employ or our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personal information. 

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit.  Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information. 

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored.  Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.  To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here:  

**6\. Disclosure of Personal Information As Required By Law**

We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) protect and defend our rights, or (c) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others. 

**7\. Business Transfers**

In the event XANGO goes through a business transition or a transfer, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, or in the unlikely event that XANGO goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, our users’ personal information may be part of the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of XANGO or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

**8\. Links**

The Site contains links to other web sites. XANGO is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every web site that collects personal information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Site. 

**9\. Social Media and Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**10\. Public Forums**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, please contact us at [service@xango.com](mailto:service@xango.com).  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**11\. Security**

XANGO takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your information. When you enter sensitive information on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. 

We also make an effort to protect your information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store your personal information are housed in a secure environment. 

When registering for access to a secure area of the Site, we will ask you to select a username and password. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, remember to sign out of the registered site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence when accessing your computer. 

If you have any questions about the security at our Site, you can send a message to the webmaster at [webmaster@xango.com](mailto:webmaster@xango.com). 

**12\. Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information**

If your personal information changes, you may contact us to correct, update or delete and deactivate our record of your personal information. We will respond to requests for access to personal information within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**13\. Testimonials**

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at [service@xango.com](mailto:service@xango.com). 

**14\. Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will prominently post a notice on the main page and other pages to alert you of the change. If the Privacy Policy changes materially so that your personal information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you by e-mail to give you a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this different manner. However, you are responsible for ensuring we have a current working e-mail address for you. If the e-mail address you have given us is incorrect or no longer operable, we will have no further obligation to notify you apart from posting the notice on our Site. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on the main page notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**15\. Contact Information**

For further information about this site or XANGO products, please contact us. 

XANGO, LLC 

2889 Ashton Blvd. 

Lehi, Utah 84043
